-- Usagi Drop Episode 11 (Final) --
Get some bread and a drink for breakfast tomorrow.
Okay!
Without running!
Does he ever listen?
Let's see... a cold means water,
sports drinks, and dairy products.
And something easy on the stomach.
Do you wanna get something too?
Maybe some cereal?
Okay.
Daikichi.
Did I pass it on to her?
Listen...
Viruses that cause colds lie everywhere.
Sometimes you get infected, sometimes you don't.
You shouldn't worry about who passed it on though.
Can I bring something for her too?
Sure.
This.
Okay, put it in here.
Kouki-kun!
What are you doing in the candy aisle?!
Kouki, what about breakfast?
It fell out!
Presented by:
Taka Fansubs
Over here!
Actually, we'll head home.
I don't want to wake your mom up.
Okay.
Here's some food for her.
It's heavy.
No kidding!
Let's go, Rin.
Okay.
Mom, Daikichi brought us food!
Do you ever hear what people say?!
Stop that, Kouki!
Daikichi-san?
Thank you so much for always watching over him!
Not at all! I should be thanking you for helping me with Rin.
How is she?
Oh, she's completely fine now.
She even went to school today.
Hello.
Hello. I'm glad you're better, Rin-chan.
Yeah.
I'm making that rice porridge again.
What?
I'll feel better soon too!
Yeah!
Rin, let's go throw my tooth!
Follow me!
Be careful, Kouki.
'Kay.
Nitani-san, you might have caught Rin's cold while taking care of her.
I'm so sorry.
Let's throw it from here!
I meet a lot of people every day.
We're so high up!
I'll aim for over there!
I go to work on a crowded train too.
Who knows whom I caught it from.
So don't worry. It's just a cold.
Alright.
At least let me take care of Kouki then.
Even if I just have to pick him up from school.
Thank you.
Rin, we're leaving.
Daikichi, let's play some games!
Sure, next time.
Kouki, be sure to watch over your mom.
Right!
Oh, yeah.
The pudding and mini-drink are from Rin.
Thank you, Rin-chan!
Pudding is my favorite food!
Good night!
Come quickly, Daikichi!
You're up early for a Sunday.
I told you I have jump-rope practice today!
Oh.
What's up?
Now this one's loose!
Brush slowly.
Okay.
And stop touching it!
Ow!
Please don't force yourself too much.
It's okay, I feel better now.
I'm sorry for relying on you all the time.
Please, it's the opposite.
I can't thank you enough.
Not at all.
I thought Kouki would be good at this.
He can't do it well just yet.
Kouki, you're jumping too soon.
You jump after it goes over your head and comes down, right?
Yeah.
Then don't use your arms and legs at the same time.
Okay.
Move your arms before your legs.
Try it once, slowly.
Okay!
Daikichi, my turn! My turn!
Okay, okay.
You're moving your arms in too big of a circle.
Keep them closer to your body.
Daikichi-san!
You're here early!
Good morning!
I guess they're morning people.
Nobu-kun's a natural.
He's got a big brother to copy, that's why.
Really?
Aren't you going to do it, Sayaka-chan?
She just lost one of her upper teeth.
Man, even little girls don't have it easy.
Sayaka-chan, what kind of case did you put your tooth in?
Did you get a cute one?
What's that?
You didn't know parents keep their kid's baby teeth in cases for memories?
Memories?
They sell lots of small cases. Cute ones too.
Small?
Cute?
Right?
Yeah.
Mine's shaped like a butterfly!
What?!
Rin would definitely love that!
Why didn't I know they sold those kinds of things?!
I feel like this always happens now that Rin's with me.
I start worrying over the smallest things.
Kaga Rin
Daikichi
Daikichi's meat and potato
stew is really delicious.
And he can run
really fast.
Daikichi, this is for you.
I made it at school.
Daikichi
And he can run
really fast.
I was supposed to write something about you.
Oh well.
It's so cute!
What is it?!
It's for when you lose your baby teeth.
It's a memory!
A memory?!
Thank you, Kouki-kun's mom!
You're welcome!
Thank you.
But isn't that Kouki's?
It's really no problem.
I throw mine out the window!
See?
But I've been throwing my teeth onto the roof all this time.
Is that okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
You can throw some and keep others.
Okay!
Rin, count me in for jump-roping too!
You're touching it again.
Let it come out on its own.
Although, regardless, it'll look like she took one to the face.
Maybe I'll tell her not to smile.
Citrus
All done.
Okay. Let's hurry and go!
Did you grow again?
You're joining in too, Daikichi-san?
I could use the exercise.
Us too.
It's not easy getting older.
I wish I could slow time down.
Wow, Daikichi-san looks like a boxer!
That's amazing!
It's less stress on my knees this way.
Really?
Daikichi, teach me how to do that!
Nope!
Why do you get to be the only one who looks cool?!
At least learn how to jump-rope normally first!
What'd you say?!
Stop it!
Teach me too!
You're good at doing it backwards, Rin-chan!
Kids are really something.
I am?
Well, they're full of energy, aren't they?
Rock, paper, scissors!
It's like they're made of energy.
Again!
Although, adults are really something too.
Adults?
You guys probably already know this, but I'm not really Rin's dad.
She's been living with me for only about a year now.
Before that, I used to live just to further my own ends,
but once she moved in with me, my life suddenly took a detour.
But you all have lived with your kids since they were born.
I know I'm still new at all this,
but do you ever have doubts about never having time for yourself?
Well, I don't!
Me neither.
Same here.
Really?
Well, you know...
Huh? What?!
Rin, wasn't the jump-rope contest today?
Yeah.
Rin.
I failed.
How many did you do?
15.
Not good!
What about backwards?
203.
What?! You jumped that many times?
Does that mean you finished first?
Yup!
Here's my certificate!
Certificate
1st Year's Group
Backwards Jump-roping, 1st Place
Kaga Rin
You really did great! This is amazing.
I could've jumped more the normal way though!
I guess they only let you go once.
Yeah...
Still, at least I know how much you improved at jump-roping.
Yeah!
I lost some!
What the?
Hey!
How much longer?
About ten minutes.
Don't forget to show them your wiggly front teeth.
Okay!
I told you to stop touching it!
I'll show them how to jump-rope too!
Okay.
I bet my parents will be shocked to see how much you've grown.
Maybe I'll be taller than your mom!
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
I should let Grandpa know too.
We're here!
Rin-chan, we've been waiting for you!
I'm home.
Look how tall you've gotten!
Are you one of the tallest in your class?
Yup!
We would have come picked you up if you had called!
It's not like she can't walk ten minutes.
You'll be taller than me at this rate!
Hi, Auntie Kazumi!
You're home early.
I just came a little bit ago.
Those clothes...
They used to be yours, right?
Yeah.
Auntie gave them to me last time!
Let me see your teeth, Rin-chan.
Okay!
My two front ones are really wiggly!
Are you okay? Do they hurt?
Sometimes they do, but they don't bother me anymore.
I'm a tooth-pro!
Daikichi!
Why didn't you help her out?!
Her gums are really red!
They're not that red...
Besides, when I was a kid, you'd threaten to pull mine out with a thread!
A thread?
Oh my, I did?
I tried to make everything easy to chew.
Thank you!
Want some freeze-dried tofu?
Okay!
Can I have some cooked beans too?
Of course!
Eat all you want!
I love freeze-dried tofu!
Did one come out?
Rin-chan?
It came out!
She's bleeding!
Mom, get a tissue!
Okay, hold on!
I'm fine!
Use this for now, Rin!
That's a wash cloth!
She's changed a lot.
I'm not sure.
Maybe this is what she's really like.
Mom told me you're getting married. Is that true?
Yeah.
That's great. He sounds like a good guy.
I guess so.
The only problem is he wants to have children right away.
Isn't that a good thing?
Who are you kidding?!
Going out drinking, going to concerts,
going on trips and tasting new foods,
I won't be able to do any of those things anymore!
You should talk to him about it then.
Don't ask me.
I'm not good with kids anyway!
And I definitely don't want to become one of those embarrassing moms!
I don't know if I could give up my lifestyle for my kid.
I think you'd manage if you really tried.
You'd have no other choice anyway.
Easier said than done, Brother.
I guess so.
What do you mean?
I'm no father or husband.
And I'm definitely not a mother.
It's done.
Right.
It's true I don't have the kind of time to go shopping or out for tea.
But, I do have time for myself at work.
And time with my son is time for me too.
It's precious.
I don't think there's anything really special about being a parent.
Just take a look around you.
There are parents everywhere!
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
Guess what, Grandpa.
My adult teeth are growing in.
Hey, Rin!
It's just sweat!
Daikichi!
Hurry!
Get ready!
Tasu
Elementary
School
Entrance
Ceremony
That vase...
Masako-san had one too.
I'll be right back!
Daikichi!
What?! Now the other one's coming out?!
I need a mirror!
I'm sure I'll keep fretting over the smallest things.
But I'm sure they all do the same too.
Does it hurt?
Rin?
Look, Daikichi!
You look like a cat, you know.
I know!
Send a picture to your parents!
It looks like I'll be happy whenever I see her smile like that.
Hurry up!
Alright, open wide!
And I think that's just fine with me.
Daikichi!